Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Demon=
=الشيطان=
=Episode 10=
=الحلقة 10=
(Moyuan City)
(مدينة مويوان)
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
Stop!
قف!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Hey, I'm talking to you!
مهلا، أنا أتحدث إليك!
Stay still!
ابقى ساكنا!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Yes, you!
نعم انت!
Look carefully.
أنظر بعناية.
Get over here!
تعال إلى هنا!
Behave!
تصرف!
Who says you can leave?
من قال لك أنه بإمكانك المغادرة؟
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Look carefully!
أنظر بعناية!
Don't let my parents know
لا تدع والدي يعرفان
about the Cat Demon
حول القط الشيطان
when we arrive home.
عندما نصل إلى المنزل.
Yes, Young Master.
نعم سيدي الشاب.
(Shen Residence)
(سكن شين)
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
you've finally returned.
لقد عدت أخيرا.
(Zhen Gui) City Lord's health is...
(Zhen Gui) صحة سيد المدينة هي ...
Mr. Zhen,
السيد تشن،
take me to my father first.
خذني إلى والدي أولاً.
Young Master, come.
سيدي الشاب، تعال.
This way, please.
من هنا من فضلك.
(Shen Residence)
(سكن شين)
Here.
هنا.
Dear, take this medicine.
عزيزي، خذ هذا الدواء.
(City Lord of Moyuan City)
(حاكم مدينة مويوان)
That's enough for now.
هذا يكفي الآن.
City Lord!
سيد المدينة!
Madam!
سيدتي!
Young Master has returned!
لقد عاد السيد الشاب!
Chen!
تشين!
Chen.
تشين.
Mother.
الأم.
Father.
أب.
I have returned.
لقد عدت.
Chen,
تشين،
I am so glad to finally see you.
أنا سعيد جدًا برؤيتك أخيرًا.
(Lady of Mo Yuan City) They said
(سيدة مدينة مو يوان) قالوا
you were caught by a Tiger Demon
لقد تم القبض عليك من قبل شيطان النمر
in Qianchun Mountain.
في جبل تشيان تشون.
I thought...
اعتقدت...
Forgive me for making you worried.
سامحني على جعلك تشعر بالقلق.
I'm just glad you're back.
أنا سعيد بعودتك.
As long as you're safe at home.
طالما أنك آمن في المنزل.
Young Lord, there's something you don't know.
يا سيدي الشاب، هناك شيء لا تعرفه.
While you were away,
بينما كنت بعيدا،
demons kept appearing in the city.
استمر ظهور الشياطين في المدينة.
The people here
الناس هنا
would rather kill a hundred by mistake
يفضل قتل مائة شخص بالخطأ
than miss one.
من أن تفوت واحدة.
Moyuan City
مدينة مويوان
is in chaos,
في حالة من الفوضى
making everyone on edge.
جعل الجميع على حافة الهاوية.
City Lord has been working day and night,
لقد كان سيد المدينة يعمل ليلًا ونهارًا،
which has worsened his old illness.
مما أدى إلى تفاقم مرضه القديم.
And your health is also...
وصحتك أيضا...
Enough!
كافٍ!
Chen just returned.
لقد عاد تشين للتو.
No need to say more.
لا داعي لقول المزيد.
Yes, Master.
نعم سيدي.
Father,
أب،
I've been unfilial.
لقد كنت عقيمًا.
I couldn't care for you while you were sick,
لم أستطع أن أعتني بك أثناء مرضك،
and I couldn't share
ولم أستطع المشاركة
the burden of the nation with you.
عبء الأمة عليك.
Chen, get up.
تشين، استيقظ.
You're not to blame.
لا يقع اللوم عليك.
So tell me.
فأخبرني.
Did your trip to the Western Regions go smoothly?
هل كانت رحلتك إلى المناطق الغربية سلسة؟
Chen,
تشين،
did you find the medicine
هل وجدت الدواء
to cure your strange illness?
لعلاج مرضك الغريب؟
Don't worry, Mother.
لا تقلقي يا أمي.
We have a lead.
لدينا تقدم.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
Zhen Gui,
تشن غوي,
go to Qianchun Mountain
اذهب إلى جبل تشيان تشون
and retrieve that medicine immediately.
واسترجاع هذا الدواء على الفور.
Mother, shouldn't we wait until things are certain
أمي، ألا يجب علينا الانتظار حتى تتأكد الأمور؟
before sending someone?
قبل إرسال شخص ما؟
Why wait?
لماذا الانتظار؟
Bring the medicine back.
احضر الدواء .
Once your illness is cured,
بمجرد شفاء مرضك،
your marriage arrangements will be easier.
ستكون ترتيبات زواجك أسهل.
When that time comes,
عندما يأتي ذلك الوقت،
I want to hold grandchildren in my arms someday.
أريد أن أحمل أحفادي بين ذراعي يومًا ما.
But Mother...
ولكن يا أمي...
Then...
ثم...
City Lord,
سيد المدينة،
Princess Huaiyang sent an invitation.
أرسلت الأميرة هوايانج دعوة.
She wants to invite Young Master
إنها تريد دعوة السيد الشاب
to have lunch at Xiaguang Restaurant the next day.
لتناول الغداء في مطعم Xiaguang في اليوم التالي.
Princess Huaiyang?
الأميرة هوايانغ؟
It's something absurd.
إنه شيء سخيف.
Last year on Chinese New Year's Eve,
في العام الماضي، في عشية رأس السنة الصينية،
Princess Huaiyang came to Moyuan City
جاءت الأميرة Huaiyang إلى مدينة Moyuan
with officials to hear the people's concerns.
مع المسؤولين لسماع هموم الشعب.
She saw you
لقد رأتك
and...
و...
She fell for you at first sight
لقد وقعت في حبك من النظرة الأولى
and hasn't forgotten you since.
ولم ينساك منذ ذلك الحين.
Not long after,
بعد فترة ليست طويلة،
she personally came to find you.
لقد أتت شخصياً للبحث عنك.
Luckily,
لحسن الحظ،
you were here because you were away looking
كنت هنا لأنك كنت بعيدًا تبحث
for medicine at the time.
للطب في ذلك الوقت.
It was absurd.
لقد كان سخيفا.
We told her
لقد قلنا لها
about your illness
عن مرضك
to decline politely.
الرفض بأدب.
Do you know what she said?
هل تعلم ماذا قالت؟
She said you're handsome
قالت أنك وسيم
and that seeing you every day would make her happy.
وأن رؤيتك كل يوم سوف يجعلها سعيدة.
What kind
اي نوع
of nonsense is that?
من هذا الهراء؟
Princess Huaiyang
الأميرة هوايانغ
is extremely headstrong.
هو عنيد للغاية.
She's definitely not a suitable match.
إنها بالتأكيد ليست مباراة مناسبة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll go see her.
سأذهب لرؤيتها.
Those are my rabbits!
هؤلاء هم أرانبي!
Give it back!
أعيدها!
What if they are rabbit spirits?
ماذا لو كانوا أرواح الأرنب؟
No! Don't!
لا! لا تفعل!
Don't kill my rabbits!
لا تقتلوا أرانبي!
It's not a demon.
إنه ليس شيطانًا.
You're the demons.
أنتم الشياطين.
Get away!
ابتعد!
You demon!
أيها الشيطان!
So it's you!
إذن أنت!
No!
لا!
You...
أنت...
How dare you get in the way of a demon slayer?
كيف تجرؤ على الوقوف في طريق قاتل الشياطين؟
Stop it, or I'll report you to the authorities.
اوقف ذلك، أو سأبلغ عنك للسلطات.
You?
أنت؟
You can't even identify demons,
لا يمكنك حتى التعرف على الشياطين،
and you want to catch them?
وتريد أن تمسك بهم؟
The strongest demon
أقوى شيطان
is right in front of you.
هو أمامك مباشرة.
Yet, you're picking
ومع ذلك، أنت تختار
a fight
قتال
with three kits?
مع ثلاث مجموعات؟
Who are you insulting?
من تهين؟
It seems like
يبدو مثل
you came to compete for the bounty.
لقد أتيت للتنافس على المكافأة.
Prepare to die!
استعد للموت!
What a trash.
يا لها من قمامة.
A demon!
شيطان!
The demon has killed someone!
لقد قتل الشيطان شخصًا!
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I am the strongest demon
أنا أقوى شيطان
in the world,
في العالم،
Fan Dayao.
فان داياو.
Go and tell your family.
اذهب وأخبر عائلتك.
Yes, it is I,
نعم، أنا هو،
Fan Dayao.
فان داياو.
The strongest demon in the world!
أقوى شيطان في العالم!
Pleased to meet you.
ممتن لمقابلتك.
We should leave.
ينبغي علينا أن نغادر.
Go home.
اذهب إلى المنزل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
(Bai)
(نعم)
Why aren't you running?
لماذا لا تركض؟
Aren't you afraid I'll tear you apart?
ألا تخاف من أن أمزقك؟
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
I think you're so cool!
أعتقد أنك رائع جدًا!
I really like you.
أنامعجب بك أيضا حقا.
You like me?
أنت تحبني؟
Thank you for saving my rabbits.
شكرا لك على إنقاذ أرانبي.
Aren't you afraid of me?
ألا تخاف مني؟
No,
لا،
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
(Like me?)
(مثلي؟)
(This kid)
(هذا الطفل)
(somehow reminds me)
(يذكرني بطريقة ما)
(of Shen Wangchen.)
(شين وانغشن.)
(Maybe she's Shen Wangchen's ally.)
(ربما هي حليفة شين وانجشين.)
Tell me!
أخبرني!
Where's Shen Wangchen?
أين شين وانغتشين؟
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
we're going home for lunch.
نحن ذاهبون إلى المنزل لتناول الغداء.
See you again.
أراك مرة أخرى.
Humans, huh?
البشر، هاه؟
If it keeps raining,
إذا استمر المطر،
I won't last much longer.
لن أستمر لفترة أطول.
(Princess Huaiyang)
(الأميرة هوايانغ)
I've heard you have a strange illness.
لقد سمعت أنك تعاني من مرض غريب.
But your complexion and appearance
لكن بشرتك ومظهرك
are flawless.
خالية من العيوب.
Your Highness, you flatter me.
صاحب السمو، أنت تملقني.
We do make
نحن نصنع
a fine pair.
زوج جيد.
Don't you think so, City Lord?
ألا تعتقد ذلك يا سيد المدينة؟
Thank you for your praise, Princess Huaiyang.
شكرا لك على الثناء، الأميرة هوايانغ.
Now that the Young Lord has returned,
الآن وقد عاد اللورد الشاب،
pack your things,
حزم أغراضك
come back to the capital with me, and tell my parents...
عد معي إلى العاصمة وأخبر والديّ...
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I already have someone I love.
لدي بالفعل شخص أحبه.
Who?
من؟
A princess?
أميرة؟
A royal princess?
أميرة ملكية؟
Or…
أو؟؟؟
To you, Princess,
إليك يا أميرتي
she's only an ordinary person.
إنها مجرد شخص عادي.
To me,
لي،
there's no one like her.
لا يوجد أحد مثلها.
I ask you to be magnanimous.
أطلب منك أن تكون كريماً.
Shen Wangchen!
شين وانغشن!
Those who caught my eye
الذين لفتوا انتباهي
have no right to refuse me!
ليس لديك الحق في رفضي!
Someone!
شخص ما!
Yes, Your Highness.
نعم سموك.
Take him back.
أعيدوه.
No.
لا.
Absolutely not.
بالتأكيد لا.
Dear,
عزيزي،
calm down.
اهدأ.
They are all royal guards.
كلهم حراس ملكيون.
If a fight breaks out,
إذا اندلع قتال،
it would offend the Emperor and bring trouble
من شأنه أن يسيء إلى الإمبراطور ويجلب المتاعب
to everyone in Moyuan City.
إلى الجميع في مدينة مويوان.
They can't get near Chen.
لا يمكنهم الإقتراب من تشين.
He knows what he's doing.
إنه يعرف ما يفعله.
Where's that wretched Shen Wangchen
أين ذلك البائس شين وانغ تشين؟
hiding?
إخفاء؟
With all this southern rain,
مع كل هذه الأمطار الجنوبية،
I'm glad I moved to the northwest.
أنا سعيد لأنني انتقلت إلى الشمال الغربي.
I have to be careful.
يجب أن أكون حذرا.
I can't turn into a cat again.
لا أستطيع أن أتحول إلى قطة مرة أخرى.
This mission is serious.
هذه المهمة خطيرة.
Everyone, come!
الجميع، تعالوا!
Look at this.
أنظر إلى هذا.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Why is there a crowd?
لماذا يوجد حشد؟
Could Shen Wangchen be there?
هل من الممكن أن يكون شين وانغ تشين هناك؟
All right, then.
حسنا إذن.
For the demon core,
بالنسبة لنواة الشيطان،
I'll give it my all.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
(Xiaoyao Inn)
(شياو ياو إن)
Look! Look!
انظر! انظر!
Stop looking.
توقف عن النظر
The City Lord's son
ابن سيد المدينة
is marrying the Princess.
يتزوج الأميرة.
A perfect match.
مباراة مثالية.
You see.
هل ترى.
The Young Lord and the Princess
اللورد الشاب والأميرة
are a pair of talent and beauty.
هما ثنائي الموهبة والجمال.
They're absolutely perfect together.
إنهم مثاليين تماما مع بعضهم البعض.
Yes, it's quite the celebration.
نعم، إنه احتفال رائع.
Young Lord? Is it Shen Wangchen?
السيد الشاب؟ هل هو شين وانغ تشين؟
I can go with you.
أستطيع أن أذهب معك.
But don't drag my family into this.
ولكن لا تجر عائلتي إلى هذا.
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
???أين فقدت اتجاهي ؟؟؟؟
♪Only emptiness is left♪
???لم يبق إلا الفراغ؟؟؟
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
???أرق، لا ينام، نحن نفترق؟؟؟
♪As sorrow slowly grows within♪
"كما ينمو الحزن ببطء في الداخل"
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
???الدموع لا يمكن أن تشفى، والابتسامات لا تزال تؤلمني؟؟؟
♪Because my heart's with you♪
???لأن قلبي معك؟؟؟
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
"نظرتك أذابت الضباب"
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
???هل انتظرت عودتك لفترة طويلة؟
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
???غروب الشمس يذكرني بك؟؟؟
♪If the clear sky is torn by storm and rain one day♪
ماذا لو تمزقت السماء الصافية بفعل العاصفة والمطر في يوم من الأيام؟
♪Tears will flow♪
???هل ستتدفق الدموع؟؟؟
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
???سوف أظل أنتظر هنا دون أي ندم؟؟؟
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
???هل انتظرت عودتك لفترة طويلة؟
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
???غروب الشمس يذكرني بك؟؟؟
♪In the amber desert, you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
???في الصحراء الكهرمانية، تبتعد والدموع في عينيك؟؟؟
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
???سأرحب بك مرة أخرى بفستان أحمر؟؟؟
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪
???الانتظار إلى الأبد دون أي ندم؟؟؟